To invoke the hive-mind representing chaos.
Invoking the feeling of chaos.
With out order.
The Nezperdian hive-mind of chaos. Zalgo.
He who Waits Behind The Wall.
ZALGO!

WARNING: Resulting text size is roughly original * (1 + fuck up level). Thou hast been warned.

NOTE: If this program crashes on thee, blame thyself for fucking up a piece of text that is too big with a very high fuck up level.

Do blame Windows for not able to show proper text in the edit control, for now, use the preview button.

Bonus Geek Info: NFD text will lose all diacritics. Thou hast been warned.
